[{"answer": "Well, I don't know the answer to that.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "I mean, in the case of Arnold Schwarzenegger, do you think if the electorate had known that he had a love child by his housekeeper he would have ever become governor of California?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "And were you aware of what transpired from January?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well, I think -- David Axelrod is right, that clearly Arnold Schwarzenegger didn't think so.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "Do you think that Arnold Schwarzenegger would have been able to become governor of California if this story had emerged before the election?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Well, I think from public figures and politicians we do expect more, particularly because they actually vote on issues of morality and intrusions into people's lives and how people's lives are conducted.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "As a traditional sex scandal, should we all just grow up a bit and accept that, you know, people will misbehave sexually and it shouldn't have any effect on their work as politicians or as leaders of banks or whatever it may be?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Well, whether it should or it does are two different things.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "Should it matter politically?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "Well, because --", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "Why is that a surprise to anybody?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "Yes, of course.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Don't you think?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Well, here's the sad part.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Could we potentially see a movie version of Tiger Woods unfold?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "Well, you know, if we're looking for moral leadership from our sports figures, from our entertainer, now from our politicians and businessmen, I think we're all looking in the wrong place.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "What's going on?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Well, I think actually we've seen -- we see more of a divergence right now, that you can get away with it in sports and in entertainment and other places.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "What was your response to that?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Well, let's separate the two.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "Would you take on Dominique Strauss-Khan?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "I think the only legitimate question for people to really complain about is the perp walk.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Is this fair or is it prejudicial?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Look, I think that it's probably not necessary.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "And what do you think?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Can we expect any privacy anymore given the existence of Twitter, social networks, Facebook and so on?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "I think that the first question is going to be, is he going to get bail.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "How do you see the legal position in relation to this IMF chief going?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "Well, I think that you -- first of all, these are always stunning developments when you hear them.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "What do you make of this whole issue?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "And -- well, I think they're all human beings, and some -- you know, are flawed, and so, you know, I think that we should -- we should put our faith in them to the degree that we know what their public positions have been, what they've done with their -- but I think it's hard to get to know people.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Should we?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know the answer to that, but I suspect the fact that it didn't become public until after suggests that he didn't necessarily believe that.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "I mean, in the case of Arnold Schwarzenegger, do you think if the electorate had known that he had a love child by his housekeeper he would ever have become governor of California?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "Well, you know, look, there's no place like the White House when things are happening.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "When you see this -- you know, almost apocalyptic series of events we've had in the world with the Middle East uprisings, with what happened in Japan, with the killing of Osama bin Laden and so on, have you missed being back in the center of things at the White House, or are you still quietly there on the end of the phone?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "It's excellent.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Is it good or the bad to have -- be seeing more of him?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, I've been asked that question a lot, and I think it's very -- one thing you're acutely aware of when you're in the White House is that there are going to be a million developments between now and November of 2012.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "I mean in terms of the politics of what's been happening, how significant do you think, particularly the bin Laden incident, may have been for the Obama election campaign that will be coming up to?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "Going through not just that seizure, but she had multiple, multiple -- dozens of seizures every single day.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Watching Lauren go through that seizure?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Totally terrifying.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "It's terrifying for new parents?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "Well, I think a number of reasons.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Why is that, do you think?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Well, I think one thing that we can do is just really -- and one of the things we've been successful at doing is changing the focus of research, which was always about sort of slapping more medications on seizures and hoping that you could just make them sort of subside.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "What are the most effective ways we can try and change this?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "We still have no idea why that drug is working.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "What a moment for you?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "It's --", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "And do you know how many other people it works on?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "And we need to understand that.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "It was for you?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Do you feel, Susan, that you've -- you've lost a life with Lauren, although she's alive and she's doing better than she was, that she's never going to lead the life that you would have hoped for when she was first born as a healthy baby?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "I just have to put it somewhere where I, you know -- I don't deal with it very well, because -- because it will get me pretty emotional.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "Does she?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "You know, epilepsy affects one to two percent of the population worldwide.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Susan, how prevalent is epilepsy in America at the moment?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "Well, there are all kinds of impacts on the family, Piers.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "What impact did it have on you financially?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "Well, they can certainly join some of the events that we're having around the country that are -- are cropping up in places that other family members --", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "If they're watching this and they either know people with epilepsy or they just want to help, what is the most effective way they can do this?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "We have a website, cureepilepsy.org.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "You have a website?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "No, I -- well, look, I believe that medical research generally needs more.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Has the government been doing enough in terms of providing funding for epilepsy research?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "Put a little pressure on them?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, one of the reasons why we have a trusting relationship is because I reserve those kinds of comments --", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "Where would the ticks be and where would the crosses be?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "Presumably, you will be involved, as you were last time?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "Well, look, you know, 16 months is an eternity in politics.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "Is the apparent chaos of the GOP at the moment an encouraging sign for you?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "Not really --", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "Are you a betting man?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "Occasional.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "An occasional dabble?", "qSentId": 678}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "If you were about to put a little bet on it, who would you think may end up, as things stand, with the Republican nomination?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 692, "question": "But as -- as things stand, it's looking pretty good for the president, isn't it?", "qSentId": 691}, {"answer": "Well, I think we take it day by day.", "docId": "110517pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "Been a good few weeks?", "qSentId": 693}]